<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://zack69.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://zack69.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-06-02T08:41:58+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://zack69.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Hangout]]></title>
    <link href="http://zack69.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/google-hangout/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-02T08:28:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://zack69.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/google-hangout</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Group conversations are better than ever
Share photos and emoji for more lively conversations</p>

<p>Whether you’re talking just with that special someone or figuring out Friday night plans with the whole gang, Hangouts are like real-life conversations. You can show photos and share how you’re feeling with emoji.</p>

<p>Have more engaging conversations</p>

<p>See when your friends have read your messages and when they’re typing back. If a friend isn’t available when you try to reach them, they’ll see an alert next time they connect, keeping your conversations alive.
Easily go back to any of your Hangouts</p>

<p>Finding your ongoing conversations across devices and picking them back up is simple. And you can scroll back through past Hangouts to re-live what you talked about — from those epic trip photos to that nice note from a friend when you were home sick.</p>

<p>Video calls make Hangouts more fun
Make video calls to connect face-to-face</p>

<p>Turn one-on-one or group conversations into live face-to-face video calls with up to 10 people at once. Catch up with friends and family even when you’re on the go, all for free.</p>

<p>You can also watch public Hangouts On Air on a diverse set of topics. See schedule</p>

<p>All your friends can use Hangouts
Everyone is invited</p>

<p>Don’t worry about what kinds of computers and phones your friends use. Hangouts works across computers and on Android phones and tablets, iPhone, iPad and iPod Touch. So you can connect with everyone, and no one gets left out.</p>

<p>Upgrade Gmail Chat to the new Hangouts experience</p>

<p>Hangouts works right inside Gmail, where Chat did before. You can upgrade Chat to Hangouts by clicking on your photo icon in Gmail&rsquo;s chat list.
Hangouts on Apple devices, for the first time</p>

<p>You and your friends can now message each other with Google on your Apple devices. Hangouts works great across iPhone, iPad and iPod touch.</p>

<p>Live-stream with Hangouts On Air
Go live from your laptop</p>

<p>Have a topic you want to share with the world? Go live in front of a global audience directly from your computer in only a few clicks. You can stream a conference keynote, host a worldwide concert or moderate a panel discussion with international experts. Learn more</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[new post]]></title>
    <link href="http://zack69.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/new-post/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-02T08:22:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://zack69.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/new-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
